cardconnect.com 2016-05-04

# 

### Last Updated: 01/14/2014

### CardConnect is committed to protecting the privacy of our website visitors. This policy outlines what information we collect from visitors on our website and how we use that information.

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of data:

1\.  Information about your visits to and use of this website;

2\.  Information that you provide to us for the purpose of inquiring about our products and services and/or subscribing to our email notifications.

## Website Visit Information

We may collect information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. We may use this information in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability, and for marketing purposes.

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

If your browser does not have cookies disabled, we may send a cookie which may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognize your computer when you visit our website, and to personalize our website for you.

If your browser does not have cookies disabled, we may also use anonymous cookies to record non-personal information such as website activity, date and time of visit, and domain type. We may use this information for retargeting purposes.  

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.  
In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may use your personal information to:

1\. Improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;

2\. Send information (other than marketing communications) to you which we think may be of interest to you by post or by email or similar technology;

3\. Send to you marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or by email or similar technology.

4\. Provide other companies with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user.

5\. Provide relevant and targeted advertisements through re-targeting. All data is anonymous and cannot be used to identify the visitor.

In addition to the disclosures identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:

1\. To the extent that we are required to do so by law;

2\. In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

3\. In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk).  

## Securing Your Personal Data

We will take all reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.  

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of third party websites.  

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to marketing (at) cardconnect.com or by post to CardConnect, 1000 Continental Drive, Suite 600, King of Prussia, PA 19406.
